Ronald Daniels

Clinical Pharmacist

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Ronald-Daniels/c58fa8c5fdbe7103

With extensive experience as a pharmacy operations manager, assistant director, supervisor, as well as in retail management, I am interested in continuing my career as a provider of clinical pharmacy service to patients and mentoring the next generation of pharmacists.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Abington Memorial Hospital - Abington, PA - November 2007 to September 2011

Reviewed and processed medication orders. Supervised the dispensing, preparation, and documentation of drugs and records for drug inventory.

Operations Manager

Northeastern Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - July 2007 to November 2007

Supervised day to day operations for pharmacy department, from coverage scheduling to ensuring compliance with Federal and State laws and Joint Commission guidelines.

Assistant Director of Pharmacy

Temple University Children's Medical Center - Philadelphia, PA - July 2005 to July 2007

Supervised day to day operations of pharmacy department.

Staff Pharmacist

Temple University Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - August 1998 to July 2005

Staffed night shift position at Temple University Hospital. Processed medication orders and supervised the dispensing and preparation of said orders. Was active member of code response team.

Staff Pharmacist

Esquire Drug Company - Philadelphia, PA - July 1993 to January 1998

Staff Pharmacist in busy independent retail setting.

Pharmacy Manager

Chane's Drug Store - Philadelphia, PA - May 1989 to July 1993

Managed independent retail pharmacy.

Staff Pharmacist/IV Coordinator

Albert Einstein Medical Center - Philadelphia, PA - July 1986 to April 1989

Staff Pharmacist and IV coordinator. Supervised the preparation and dispensing of intravenous medications.

EDUCATION

B.S. in Pharmacy in Pharmacy

Temple University School of Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA January 1979 to January 1984

B. S. in Biology in Biology

St.Lawrence University - Canton, NY January 1975 to January 1979

SKILLS

Microsoft Office, Inventory Management